Search

Privacy Policy

By creating your account with us, you confirm that you have read, understood, and agree to the provisions of this Privacy Policy and to our Terms of Service. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for zoogvpn.com & ZoogVPN products.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [\[email protected\]](https://zoogvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

From time to time, ZoogVPN may introduce new products and services. To the extent that these new products and services affect this policy, this policy will be updated.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 2004 (the “Act”) and Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council (GDPR) (together the “Data Protection Legislation”), the data controller is Zoog Services PC a company incorporated in Greece and registered in Greece with Company Number 145382616000 whose registered office is at 130 Germanou Str, Postcode. 26224, Patras, Greece, email: [\[email protected\]](https://zoogvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Principles Relating to Processing of Personal Data**

In the course of processing personal data, the Zoog Services PC as Data Controller observes and acts in line with the following principles stipulated in Article 5 of the GDPR:

**Lawfulness, fairness, and transparency** – this means that your personal data will be collected, stored, and processed lawfully and fairly and we will be transparent with you about the manner in which we do so

**Purpose limitation** – this means that we will only collect your personal data for specific legitimate purposes and we will not process your personal data in a manner which would contradict those purposes

**Data minimization** – this means that the personal data we collect will be limited to what is adequate and relevant in relation to the purpose for which we have collected it

**Accuracy** – this means that we will keep personal data we hold about you accurate and up to date

**Storage limitation** – which means that we will only collect, store and process your personal data only for as long as is necessary (in connection with the purpose for which we have collected it)

**Integrity and confidentiality** – which means that we will keep personal data that we collect, store, and process about you secure.

### What is ZoogVPN, and why is my information needed?

ZoogVPN provides the registered user with secure and fast access to the Internet from any location. ZoogVPN makes the VPN service available under a number of different subscription plans. ZoogVPN requires a valid email address for account management as a login and a valid password during the registration process.

### Does ZoogVPN store any user information, and how is it used?

We pride ourselves on being a **zero-logs** VPN service. We only collect your email address (which can be a disposable one) because of the nature of our service. However, for account management purposes we strongly recommend you use an active mailbox to both receive and send emails, for ZoogVPN service. Your email address will never be given away or sold. Your email will be used only to deliver ZoogVPN services, communicate with you about your subscription, promotions, support, and generally maintain your account with us. We strictly do not share, sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties.

We have adopted ‘Zero Logs’ policy and are not required to collect any by our jurisdiction. This means we do not keep any logs of your online activity so you can browse with 100% privacy and confidence.

We strictly do not collect or keep any usage information on user activity, the websites or apps the user visits, timestamps, user IP addresses, or user log-in/log-out sessions. However, for the purpose of rendering VPN service, we collect total data transferred on our servers as aggregated upload/download.

ZoogVPN service by necessity requires us to provide the user’s email address to payment processors e.g. Paypal for processing credit card or Paypal payments. They only have access to the user’s email address required to perform their function and may not use it for other purposes. They are contractually obligated to keep all data confidential. Your information is at all times encrypted and secured.

### How does ZoogVPN protect my information from loss, misuse, or alteration?

ZoogVPN uses industry-leading technologies to safeguard the confidentiality of personally identifiable information, including encryption, firewalls, and SSL (Secure Sockets Layer).

### Who should I ask if I have further questions?

For additional inquiries about the privacy of your information, you can contact ZoogVPN via email at [\[email protected\]](https://zoogvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Zoog Services IKE

130 Germanou, Patras 26224, Greece

+1 321 396 5183

##### About ZoogVPN

##### Help and Support

##### Partnership

Copyright © 2024 **ZoogVPN.com**

CLOSE

Try Premium risk-free
---------------------

If it’s not right for you, we’ll refund you.

🔥  Streaming services and 1000+ unblocked sites

🔥  200+ servers across 35+ countries

🔥  Advanced security features

🔥  Protect 10 devices at a time

7 days money-back guarantee
